Bring your nightmares to life.
Stopmotion is a horror, animation film directed by Robert Morgan.
Ella Blake, a stop-motion animator struggling to control her demons after the loss of her overbearing
mother, embarks upon the creation of a film that becomes the battleground for her sanity.
As Ella’s mind starts to fracture, the characters in
her project take on a life of their own.
Ella Blake, played by Aisling Franciosi.
Suzanne Blake, played by Stella Gonet.
Tom, played by Tom York.
Polly, played by Therica Wilson-Read.
Doctor Rai, played by Bridgitta Roy.
Little Girl, played by Caoilinn Springall.
Stopmotion is a 2023 British live-action/adult animated psychological horror-thriller film directed by
Robert Morgan in his feature-length debut, from a screenplay he wrote with Robin King.
The film stars Aisling Franciosi as a stop motion animator who becomes
increasingly obsessed with a film she is working on.
Stopmotion was released on 23 February 2024 to critical acclaim.
The film explores themes of stop motion, adult
animation, live action and animation.
The tone is dark.